<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<Module>
  <ModulePrefs title="ABVA Home Gadget" height="100">
    <Require feature="dynamic-height"/> 
  </ModulePrefs>
  <UserPref name="siteDomain" display_name="Site Domain" datatype="string" required="true"/>
  <UserPref name="siteName" display_name="Site Name" datatype="string" required="true"/>
  <UserPref name="siteRoot" display_name="Site Root" datatype="string" required="true"/>
  
  <Content type="html">
     <![CDATA[

    <meta charset="utf-8">
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1, shrink-to-fit=no">
    <meta name="description" content="">
    <meta name="author" content="">

    <!-- Bootstrap core CSS -->
    <link href="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/bootstrap/bootstrap.min.css" rel="stylesheet">

    <!-- Custom styles for this template -->
    <link href="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/carousel.css" rel="stylesheet">
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/graph.css">
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/mcdp.css">
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://abvasvmc.github.io/aim-centre/aim-centre.css">

    <script src="https://ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/3.2.1/jquery.min.js" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="//cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/Chart.js/2.1.2/Chart.min.js"></script>
    <script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.12.9/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-ApNbgh9B+Y1QKtv3Rn7W3mgPxhU9K/ScQsAP7hUibX39j7fakFPskvXusvfa0b4Q" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
    <script src="https://maxcdn.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.0.0/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-JZR6Spejh4U02d8jOt6vLEHfe/JQGiRRSQQxSfFWpi1MquVdAyjUar5+76PVCmYl" crossorigin="anonymous"></script> 

    <script type="text/javascript" src="//cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/Chart.js/2.1.2/Chart.min.js"></script>
    <script src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/chroma.min.js" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>     
    <script src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/graph.js" crossorigin="anonymous"></script> 


    <main role="main">

      <div id="myCarousel" class="carousel slide carousel-fade" data-ride="carousel">
        
        <div class="d-none d-md-block">
          <ol class="carousel-indicators">
            <li data-target="#myCarousel" data-slide-to="0" class="active"></li>
            <li data-target="#myCarousel" data-slide-to="1"></li>
          </ol>
        </div>
        
        <div class="carousel-inner">
          <div class="carousel-item active">
            <div class="img first-slide" style='background-image: url("https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/banner_p1.jpg")'></div>
          </div>
          <div class="carousel-item">
            <div class="img second-slide" style='background-image: url("https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/banner_p2.jpg")'></div>
          </div>
        </div>
      </div>

		<ul class="nav nav-tabs">
			<li class="active"><a data-toggle="tab" class="active" href="#English">English</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;</li>
			<li><a data-toggle="tab" href="#Sinhala" class="sinhala">සිංහල</a></li>
		</ul>  
		<div class="tab-content">
			<div id="English" class="tab-pane active">
			  <div class="row">
			    <div class="col-lg-7">
			      <h1>AIM Centre Development</h1>
            <div class="content-image">
              <img src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/aim-centre/images/model-1.jpg" alt="Generic placeholder image">
            </div>            
			      <p>
			        Our goal is to build the infrastructure facilities required to host the range of meditation, mindfulness, stress-relief, moral &amp; ethical development and cultural programs offered by our meditation centre on the serene land we were able to acquire thanks to the tremendous generosity of our well wishers. This facility will have optimized spaces for conducting meditation programs, classes, workshops and social events. The facility will be accessible to the community without limiting on one’s origin, ethnicity, culture or beliefs.
			      </p>
			      <p>
			        We welcome funds and expertise from all possible sources, groups and individuals to timely complete this project. We truly acknowledge the unprecedented support we received so far in terms of financially, guidance, and hands-on help from the community and we are committed to complete the rest of this project with the same level of transparency and respect that we exhibited so far.
			      </p>
			      <p>
			        We are currently in the process of designing the facility. We will implement it as a series of milestones, prioritized based on the needs and resources. Each milestone will deliver a well-designed permanent solution towards the final goal. We will publish full details of each milestone online timely and we will respect your feedback and help. 
			      </p>
			    </div> <!-- col-lg-7 -->
			    <div class="col-lg-5 sidebar">
			      <div class="sidebar-section-title">Upcoming Milestones</div>
			      <div class="sidebar-content">
			        <h3>Pathway Lighting</h3>
              <div class="sidebar-image">
		            <img src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/aim-centre/images/park-lights.jpg" alt="Generic placeholder image">
              </div>
			        <p>
			          As one of the very first milestones of the AIM Centre Development project, we expect to install outdoor lighting on the 350 metre pathway from the property entrance to the present house. We have obtained preliminary directions from the Parkland County and we are about to deisgn the lighting system. If you have expertise in design or installation of outdoor lighting, please <a href="mailto:president@abva.org">contact us</a>; we need help. The installation will commence in Spring 2019. More details to come soon.
			        </p>
			      </div>
			      <div class="sidebar-section-title">Archive</div>
			      <div class="sidebar-content">
			        <h3>Property Purchase Fund</h3>
			        <p>
			          Much merits to everyone who contributed the nearly $350,000 property-purchase fund. This fund was started in June 2018 and received unprecedented support from many of you to timely raise funding for the  purchase of the serene property in Parkland. You may view the details on the <a href="http://abva.org/aim/property-purchase-fund" target="_top">property-purchase fund</a> page.
			        </p>
			      </div>
			    </div><!-- col-lg-5 -->
			  </div><!-- row -->

			  <hr class="featurette-divider">

			  <div class="featurette">
			    <h1>Contribution Options</h1>
          <p>
            You can contribute to this meritorious project in many ways. These include, but are not limited to, sharing your design or construction expertiese, sponsoring for materials or services, and making financial contributions.
          </p> 
          <p>
            We would like to kindly request you to consider making a pre-authorized monthly donation as well, if that's possible. This will tremendously help us pay the mortgage obtained from the Servus Credit Union. Please contact Suditha at <a href="mailto:donations@abva.org">donations@abva.org</a> for details.
          </p>
          <p> 
            Since we are a registered, charitable, non-profit organization with the Canada Revenue Agency, we will be able to provide an official tax receipt for all material sponsorships and financial contributions. You can estimate the tax credit you will receive by using the <a href="http://www.cra-arc.gc.ca/chrts-gvng/dnrs/svngs/clmng1b2-eng.html" target="_blank"><span class="font-weight-bold">Charitable Donation Tax Credit Calculator</span></a>.  The credit is based on your total annual charitable contributions made.
          </p>
			  </div>

			</div> <!-- English tab -->

			<div id="Sinhala" class="tab-pane fade sinhala">
			  <div class="row">
			    <div class="col-lg-7">
			      <h1>පන්සල් පරිශ්‍රය ගොඩ නැංවීම</h1>
            <div class="content-image">
              <img src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/aim-centre/images/model-1.jpg" alt="Generic placeholder image">
            </div>                        
			      <p>
			      සැදැහැවත් ඔබගේ පුණ්‍යවන්ත දායකත්වයෙන් නවමු ස්ථානයක පිහිටුවනු ලැබූ අපේ පන්සලෙහි අනාගත සැළසුම් පිළිබඳව මෙලෙස ඔබව දැනුවත් කරන්නට කැමැත්තෙමු. 
			      </p>
			      <p>
			       ස්වභාවික සුන්දර වටපිටාවක පිහිටි අපේ පන්සල් භුමිය සියලු දෙනාටම සැදැහැ උපදවන ප්‍රිය උපදවන අයුරින් නිර්මාණය කිරීම අපගේ අපේක්ෂාවයි. එහි ප්‍රධාන පියවර වනුයේ විහාර මන්දිරයක් හා දහම් පාසලට ගොඩනැගිල්ලක් ඉදිකිරීමයි. 
			      </p>
			      <p>
			        බුද්ධ මන්දිරයක් ඉදිකිරිම යනු සැමදා පින් වැඩෙන පින්කමක් බව ඔබ අප සියලු දෙනාම ඉතාමත් හොඳින් දන්නා කරුණකි. සිය දහස් ගණනකගේ අතිශය වන්දනාවට භාජනය වන තථාගතයන් වහන්සේ වෙනුවෙන් ආරාමයක් ඉදිකරන්නට යමෙකුට අවස්ථාව ලැබෙන්නේ ඉතාමත් කලාතුරකිනි. ඒ උතුම් පිංකම සිදුකරන්නට ඔබ සිටින පරිසරයෙන්ම අවස්ථාවක් උදාවීම කොතරම් පුණ්‍යවන්ත ද. එසේම සසර දුකෙන් මිදෙන්නට තථාගත දේශනාව අනුව සිත පුහුණු කරන්නට වෙහෙසන සැදැහැවතුනට ඒ වෙනුවෙන් පහසුකම් සැළසීම අපට ද ඒ මග ගමන් කරන්නට සුදුසුකම් සපුරා ගැනීමකි. 
			      </p>
			      <p>
			        අනාගත පරපුර වන දරු පරපුරට අපගේ සාරධර්ම ඉගැන්වීම ඔබේ ඒකායන අපේක්ෂාවයි. අපෙන් පසුව අපේ උරුමය ඉදිරියට ගෙනයන අපගේ දරුවන් වෙනුවෙන් ගුණ දහම් උගන්වන්නට සුදුසු පරිදි පහසුකම් සැළසීම අපගේ වගකීමයි. එක සිතින් උත්සාහ කළොත් ඒ පියවරද අපට ජයගත හැකිවේ. 
			        ඒ සඳහා වන අලංකාරවත් ගෘහ නිර්මාණ සැළැස්මක් මේ වනවිටත් සකසමින් පවතින බව සතුටු සිතින් යුතුව ඔබට දැනුම්දෙන්නට කැමැත්තෙමු. 
			      </p>
			      <p>
			        මේ සියලු වැඩපිළිවෙලෙහි කටයුතු ඉතා ඉක්මනින් ආරම්භ කිරීම අපගේ බලාපොරොත්තුවයි. එහි පළමු අදියර වශයෙන් ඉතා නොබෝදිනකින් ම පන්සල් භුමියේ පිවිසුම් මාර්ගය විදුලි පහන් කණු යොදා අලංකාරවත් ලෙස ආලෝක කිරීම සිදුකරනු ලැබේ. එම මූලික කටයුතු නිමකොට ලබන වසරේ මුල් කාලය තුළ යටකී ගොඩනැගීම් ආරම්භ කිරීම ද සිදුකරනු ලැබෙති. 
			      </p>
			      <p>
			        මෙතෙක් සිදුකළ කටයුතු සියල්ල ඔබව දැනුවත් කරමින් ඔබගේ ද අදහස් ගරුකරමින් සිදුකලාක් මෙන් ඉදිරි කටයුතුද එලෙසම සිදු කිරීම අපගේ අපේක්ෂාවයි.
			      </p>
			    </div> <!-- col-lg-7 -->
			    <div class="col-lg-5 sidebar">
			      <div class="sidebar-section-title">ඉදිරි පියවර </div>
			      <h3>මාවත ආලෝකකරණය</h3>
              <div class="sidebar-image">
                <img src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/aim-centre/images/park-lights.jpg" alt="Generic placeholder image">
              </div>
			      <p>
			        පන්සල ගොඩනැගීමේ වැඩ පිළිවෙලේ එක් මූලික අදියරක් ලෙස පන්සල් පරිශ්‍රයට ඇතුළු වූ තැන සිට දැනට ඇති විහාරස්ථාන ගොඩනැගිල්ල දක්වා ඇති මීටර 350ක පමණ වූ මාර්ගය ආලෝකකරණය කිරීමේ ව්‍යාපෘතියක් මේ වනවිට සැලසුම් කරමින් පවතින බව සතුටින් දැනුම් දෙමු. මේ සඳහා අවශ්‍ය මුලික තොරතුරු දැනට අප සතුව ඇති අතර, එහි සැලසුම්කරණයට ඔබට සහාය විය හැකිනම් ඒ බව අපට කාරුණිකව දැනුම් දෙන්න. මේ සඳහා අපට සහාය අවශ්‍යව ඇත. මෙම ව්‍යාපෘතිය ලබන වසරේ වසන්ත සමය තුල ක්‍රියාවට නැංවීම අපගේ බලාපොරොත්තුවයි. වැඩි දුර විස්තර ළඟදීම ඔබ වෙත ගෙන එමු.
			      </p>

			      <div class="sidebar-section-title">ආ මගක සටහන්</div>
			      <h3>ආරාම පූජා අරමුදල</h3>
            <p>
              ආරාම භූමිය මිලදී ගැනීම සඳහා 2018 ජූනි මස ආරම්භ කල අරමුදලට මාස කිහිපයක කාලයක් තුල අපගේ දායක පින්වතුන් විසින් ඩොලර් 350,000 කට ආසන්න මුදලක් පරිත්‍යාග කර මහඟු පුණ්‍ය කර්මයක් සිදුකල බව ගෞරවයෙන් සඳහන් කරමු. ඔබ විසින් කල ඒ කැප කිරීමේ ප්‍රතිඵලයක් ලෙස අප පන්සලට අද ඇති රමණීය භූමිය ලබා ගතහැකි විය. ඒ පිළිබඳව අප පුණ්‍යානුමොදනා පූර්වකව සිහිපත් කරන අතර, එහි වැඩිදුර තොරතුරු මෙම වෙබ් පිටුවෙහි ඇති බව සඳහන් කරනු කැමැත්තෙමු.
            </p>
			    </div><!-- col-lg-5 -->
			  </div> <!-- row -->

			  <hr class="featurette-divider">

			  <div class="row featurette">
          <div class="col-lg-12">
			     <h1>ඔබට දායක වියහැකි අයුරු</h1>
         </div>
			  </div>

			</div> <!-- Sinhala tab -->
		</div> <!-- tab-content -->

		<hr class="featurette-divider">

    </main>

    <!-- Bootstrap core JavaScript
    ================================================== -->
    <!-- Placed at the end of the document so the pages load faster -->
    
    <script src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/bootstrap/popper.min.js"></script>
    <script src="https://abvasvmc.github.io/capital/bootstrap/bootstrap.min.js"></script>

    <script type="text/javascript">

      function resetCarouselSize(){
        var width = $(window).width();
        var aspectRatio = 1900/540;
        var height = Math.round(width / aspectRatio);
        $("#myCarousel .carousel-item").height(height);
        $("#myCarousel .carousel-item .img").height(height);

        gadgets.window.adjustHeight();
      }

      $(function() {
        resetCarouselSize();
//        initialize("graphPanel", "donorNames", true, 700000, "pledgeDistributionPanel");
        $('.carousel').carousel({
          "pause": false,
          "interval": 8000
        });
      });

      $( window ).resize(function() {
        resetCarouselSize();
      });

    </script>

     ]]>
  </Content> 
</Module>